Guide to the Abraham Hayward correspondence files: 1063 items, 1790-1889
The New York Public Library. Carl H. Pforzheimer Collection of Shelley and His Circle.
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 July 1862; HWD 01.076; envelope only
- Holland, Mary Augusta Coventry Fox, Baroness, 1812-1889, St. Anne's Hill, Chertsey - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 January 1877; HWD 02.019; autograph letter signed
- Hook, Theodore Edward, 1788-1841, HWD 08.025; autograph letter signed
- Howden, John Hobart Caradoc, Baron, 1799-1873, Madrid - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 February 1857; HWD 01.087; autograph letter signed
  With note to Howden from [?].
- Jameson, Mrs. (Anna), 1794-1860, Vienna - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 July 1835; HWD 07.053; autograph letter signed
- Kilbracken, Arthur Godley, Baron, 1847-1932, 10 Downing Street, Whitehall - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 May 1880; HWD 04.093; autograph letter signed
- Kimberley, John Wodehouse, Earl of, 1826-1902, Kimberley House, Wymondham, Norfolk - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 January 1848; HWD 09.032; autograph letter signed
- Kinglake, Alexander William, 1809-1891, Wilton House, Taunton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, October 1856; MISC 3519; autograph letter signed
- Kingsdown, Thomas Pemberton-Leigh, Baron, 1793-1867 - to [?], 22 July 1886; HWD 08.085; autograph letter signed
- L. E. L. (Letitia Elizabeth Landon), 1802-1838, 22 [Hans?] Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 03.027; autograph letter signed
- Lamington, Alexander Dundas Ross Wishart Cochrane-Baillie, Baron, 1816-1890 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.058; autograph letter signed
- Lamington, Alexander Dundas Ross Wishart Cochrane-Baillie, Baron, 1816-1890 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.075; autograph letter signed
- Landseer, Edwin Henry, Sir, 1802-1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 August 1847; HWD 07.055; autograph letter signed
- Landseer, Edwin Henry, Sir, 1802-1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 October 1850; HWD 10.097; autograph letter signed
- Landseer, Edwin Henry, Sir, 1802-1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 February 1863; HWD 10.075; autograph letter signed
- Landseer, John George, 1763/9-1852 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 March 1858; HWD 01.068; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863, Berkeley Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Wednesday eve"; MISC 3500; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.077; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863, Richmond Hill - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, MISC 3499; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.085; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 January 1861; HWD 10.084; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 December 1853; HWD 10.078; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.025; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.026; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, [1855]; HWD 10.082; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 August 1860; HWD 10.081; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, [1858]; HWD 10.080; autograph letter signed
- Lansdowne, Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice, Marquess of, 1780-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 January 1859; HWD 10.083; autograph letter signed
- Lardner, Dionysius, 1793-1859, HWD 03.055; autograph note
  "Autograph of James Montgomery, author of The World Before the Flood" - in the hand of Dionysius Lardner; on a letter cover addressed to him from Montgomery.
- Lardner, Dionysius, 1793-1859, Regent's Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 January 1832; HWD 05.067; autograph note
  letter wrapper once holding an autograph of "Sismondi, author of the 'Italian Rambles, ' ...".
  letter wrapper once holding an autograph of "Sismondi, author of the 'Italian Rambles' ...".
- Lawson, Wilfrid, Sir, 1829-1906 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 October 1869; HWD 08.029; autograph letter signed
- Le Flo, Adolphe, 1804-1887, Jersey (Angleterre) - to [Monsieur le Ministre], 24 May 1852; HWD 08.026; autograph letter signed
- Lennox, William Pitt, Lord, 1799-1881, 23 Botton Street, Picadilly W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 May 1858; HWD 06.053; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 November 1847; HWD 03.052; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 November 1847; HWD 10.093; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 February 1863; HWD 10.101; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 25 July 1859; HWD 10.100; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 November 1847; HWD 10.094; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863, Hampton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 January 1857; HWD 10.090; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 July 1859; HWD 10.096; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863, Downing St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 March 1855; HWD 02.045; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 December 1858; HWD 02.037; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 November 1858; HWD 02.038; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863, Hampton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 October 1858; HWD 02.039; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863, Grove Mill House - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 November 1847; HWD 02.044; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 July 1853; HWD 02.040; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863, Home Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 02.036; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863, Hampton - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 December 1858; HWD 05.025; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 July 1859; HWD 02.035; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, George Cornewall, Sir, 1806-1863, Downing St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 March 1857; HWD 02.043; autograph letter signed
- Lewis, Theresa, Lady, 1803-1865, Kent House - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801, 5 March 1863; HWD 10.060; autograph letter signed
- Lightfoot, Joseph Barber, 1828-1889 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801, 21 January 1875; HWD 08.031; autograph letter signed
- Lisgar, John Young, Baron, 1807-1876, Batlieborough Castle, Batlieborough - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801, 20 October 1860; HWD 01.099; autograph letter signed
- Lisgar, John Young, Baron, 1807-1876, Carfu, 21 October 1858; HWD 01.098; autograph letter signed
- Lisgar, John Young, Baron, 1807-1876, Quebec, 8 October 1853; HWD 02.026; autograph letter signed
- Lisgar, John Young, Baron, 1807-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 May 1855; HWD 01.062; autograph letter signed
- Lisgar, John Young, Baron, 1807-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 June 1863; HWD 01.094; autograph letter signed
- Lisgar, John Young, Baron, 1807-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 April 1854; HWD 01.060; autograph letter signed
- Lisgar, John Young, Baron, 1807-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 November 1857; HWD 01.097; autograph letter signed
- Locker-Lampson, Frederick, 1821-1895, Traveller's Club, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 14 January [no year]; HWD 02.042; autograph letter signed
- Lowe, Georgiana Orred, d. 1884 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.023; autograph letter signed
  Wife of Robert Lowe, Viscount Sherbrooke.
- Lowry-Corry, Alice Margaret Greg, d. 1932, 8 Eaton Square - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 05.083; autograph letter signed
- Lyndhurst, Georgiana Goldsmith Copley, Baroness, 1807?-1901, 5 Eaton Square S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 18011884, 16 June 1875; HWD 04.030; autograph letter signed
- Lyndhurst, Georgiana Goldsmith Copley, Baroness, 1807?-1901, 5 Eaton Square S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 18011884, 11 June [no year]; HWD 04.029; autograph letter signed
- Lyndhurst, John Singleton Copley, Baron, 1772-1863, George St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 18011884, 23 May [no year]; HWD 05.063; autograph letter signed
- Lyndhurst, John Singleton Copley, Baron, 1772-1863 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.032; autograph letter signed
- Lyndhurst, John Singleton Copley, Baron, 1772-1863, George Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 18011884, 11 February 1863; HWD 06.079; autograph letter signed
- Lyndhurst, John Singleton Copley, Baron, 1772-1863, George Street - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 18011884, HWD 01.024; autograph letter signed
- Lyndhurst, John Singleton Copley, Baron, 1772-1863, Hyde Park Terrace - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 18011884, HWD 01.025; autograph letter signed
- Lyons, Richard Bickerton Pemell Lyons, Earl, 1817-1887, Paris - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 18011884, 11 April 1868; MISC 3508; autograph letter signed
- Lysons, Samuel, 1806-1877, Hempstead Court - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 18 July 1861; HWD 03.080; autograph letter signed
- Lyttelton, George William Lyttelton, Baron, 1817-1876 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 2 December 1864; HWD 10.046; autograph letter signed
- Lyttelton, George William Lyttelton, Baron, 1817-1876, 42 Portland Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 January 1875; HWD 03.067; autograph letter signed
- Lytton, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.003; autograph letter signed
- Lytton, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873, Argyll Hill - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 January 1868; HWD 07.106; autograph letter signed
- Lytton, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 August 1872; HWD 07.107; autograph letter signed
- Lytton, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 November 1861; HWD 02.002; autograph letter signed
- Lytton, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873, Argyll Hill - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 December 1869; HWD 07.108; autograph letter signed
- Lytton, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873, Knebworth House, Stevenage - to [?], HWD 06.005; autograph letter signed
- Lytton, Edward Bulwer Lytton, Baron, 1803-1873 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 June 1871; HWD 07.109; autograph letter signed
- Mackenzie, G. Muir (Georgina Muir), d. 1874, Vienna - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 September [no year]; HWD 09.007; autograph letter signed
- Mackenzie, G. Muir (Georgina Muir), d. 1874 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday"; HWD 04.046; autograph letter signed
- Mackenzie, G. Muir (Georgina Muir), d. 1874 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 June 1865; HWD 02.013; autograph letter signed
- Mackintosh, James, Sir, 1765-1832, Cadogen Place - to [?], 5 May 1826; HWD 08.018; autograph letter signed
  re: Clarendon manuscripts.
- Maclean, Charles Hope - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 April [no year]; HWD 04.054; autograph letter signed
- Macpherson, W, 48, Inverness Terrace - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 March 1861; HWD 05.089; autograph letter signed
  Macpherson, William (1812-1893), legal writer.
- Macready, William Charles, 1793-1873, Sherborne House, Sherborne, Dorset - to [?], 14 June 1851; HWD 08.028; autograph letter signed
  re: college fees.
- Malcolm, George, Sir, 1818-1897, 67 Sloane St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 March [no year]; HWD 08.004; autograph letter signed
- Manchester, William Drogo Montagu, Duke of, 1823-1890, Manchester - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 December 1872; HWD 08.017; autograph letter signed
- Manners, John, Lady - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 July 1874; HWD 03.066; autograph letter signed
  stationery: "Her Majesty's Post Master General".
- Manning, Henry Edward, 1808-1892, Archbishop's House, Westminster, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 April 1875; HWD 08.020
  Letter third person.
- Marie, Princess of Lichetenstein, 1850-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 November 1872; HWD 02.029; autograph letter signed
- Marie, Princess of Lichetenstein, 1850-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 02.031; autograph letter signed
- Marie, Princess of Lichetenstein, 1850-1878 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 August 1872; HWD 02.030; autograph letter signed
- Marie, Princess of Lichetenstein, 1850-1878, Vienna - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 January 1873; HWD 02.028; autograph letter signed
- Markham, John, Captain, b. 1797, 18 Surrey St, Strand - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 January 1855; HWD 08.078; autograph letter signed
- May, Thomas Erskine, 1815-1886, House of Commons - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 December 1868; HWD 05.062; autograph letter signed
- Merivale, Herman, 1806-1874 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Monday"; HWD 10.103; autograph letter signed
- Meves, Augustus, 37 George St. Euston Sq. N. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 13 March 1877; HWD 03.082; autograph letter signed
- Minto, Emma Elliot-Murray-Kynynmound, Countess, d. 1882 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 21 August 1868; MISC 3529; autograph letter (fragment)
- Mitford, Mary Russell, 1787-1855, Three Mile Cross - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 June 1836; HWD 02.003; autograph letter signed
- Mitford, Mary Russell, 1787-1855, 35 Norfolk Street, Strand - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 July 1834; HWD 07.050; autograph letter signed
- Mohl, Mary Clarke, 1793-1883 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 May 1866; HWD 04.097; autograph letter signed
- Moira, John Rawdon, Earl of, 1720-1793 - to [?], 3 July 1790; HWD 08.019; autograph letter signed
  re: his correspondent's "ingenious Essay".
- Moira, John Rawdon, Earl of, 1720-1793 - to [J. Ridge?], 25 November 1808; HWD 08.021; autograph letter signed
- Molesworth, William, Sir, 1810-1855, Office of Works - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 02.025; autograph letter signed
- Molesworth, William, Sir, 1810-1855 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 May 1854; HWD 01.059; autograph letter signed
- Molíns, María del Carmen de Aguirre-Solarte y Alcíbar, Marquesa de, Madrid - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 November [no year]; HWD 06.029; autograph letter signed
- Monck, Charles Stanley Monck, Viscount, 1819-1894 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 24 November 1871; HWD 09.039; autograph letter signed
- Monck, Charles Stanley Monck, Viscount, 1819-1894, Quebec - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 29 November 1866; HWD 09.040; autograph letter signed
- Monck, Charles Stanley Monck, Viscount, 1819-1894, Spencer Wood, Quebec - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 July 1867; HWD 09.037; autograph letter signed
- Monck, Charles Stanley Monck, Viscount, 1819-1894 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 November 1855; HWD 01.071; autograph letter signed
- Monck, Charles Stanley Monck, Viscount, 1819-1894, Ottawa - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 April 1868; HWD 09.041; autograph letter signed
- Monck, Charles Stanley Monck, Viscount, 1819-1894 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 November 1870; HWD 09.038; autograph letter signed
- Monck, Charles Stanley Monck, Viscount, 1819-1894, Ottawa - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 11 April 1868; HWD 09.042; autograph letter signed
- Monck, Charles Stanley Monck, Viscount, 1819-1894, Austria - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 July 1862; HWD 02.027; autograph letter signed
- Morgan, Lady (Sydney), 1783-1859 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 December 1854; HWD 07.054; autograph letter signed
- Morgan, Lady (Sydney), 1783-1859 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 9 November 1858; HWD 01.033; autograph letter signed
- Morgan, Lady (Sydney), 1783-1859 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, MISC 3501; autograph letter signed
- Morgan, Thomas Charles, Sir, 1783-1843, 91 William St - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 16 June [no year]; HWD 07.097; autograph letter signed
- Morley, John, 1838-1923, Garrick Club - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 January 1867; MISC 3521; autograph letter signed
- Morley, John, 1838-1923, Pall Mall Gazette Northumberland Street, Strand - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 November 1881; HWD 01.004; autograph letter signed
- Mortlock, Ethel, 74 Thisle Grove - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Monday"; HWD 03.031; autograph letter signed
- Mortlock, Ethel, 74, Thistle Grove, S. Kensington - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Friday"; HWD 04.090; autograph letter signed
- Mortlock, Ethel, 74 Thisle Grove - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Thursday"; HWD 04.050; autograph letter signed
- Mount-Temple, William Francis Cowper-Temple, Baron, 1811-1888, Brocket - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 September 1869; HWD 04.095; autograph letter signed
- Mount-Temple, William Francis Cowper-Temple, Baron, 1811-1888, The Athenaeum - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 09.060; autograph letter signed
- Mount-Temple, William Francis Cowper-Temple, Baron, 1811-1888 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Monday"; HWD 03.028; autograph letter signed
- Mount-Temple, William Francis Cowper-Temple, Baron, 1811-1888, 15 Gt. Stanhope Street W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Saturday"; HWD 03.032; autograph letter signed
- Mount-Temple, William Francis Cowper-Temple, Baron, 1811-1888 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 26 November 1858; HWD 04.101; autograph letter signed
- Mundy, Godfrey Charles, 1804-1860, 2 Chester Place - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 3 July 1852; HWD 07.039; autograph letter signed
- Mundy, Godfrey Charles, 1804-1860, Ampthill - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 31 August 1852; HWD 07.040; autograph letter signed
- Napier, Macvey, 1776-1847 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 6 March 1845; HWD 03.048; autograph letter signed
- Napier, Macvey, 1776-1847 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.049; autograph letter signed
- Napier, Macvey, 1776-1847 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 12 April 1845; HWD 03.054; autograph letter signed
- Napier, Macvey, 1776-1847 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 03.053; autograph letter signed
- Napier, Macvey, 1776-1847 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 April 1845; HWD 03.050; autograph letter signed
- Newcastle, Henry Pelham, Duke of, 1811-1864, Chamber - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 30 January 1859; MISC 3513; autograph letter signed
- Northbrook, Thomas George Baring, Earl of, 1826-1904, War Office - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 July 1871; HWD 02.063; autograph letter signed
- O'Neill, Eliza, 1791-1872 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 23 September 1871; HWD 04.052; autograph letter signed
  Signed "E. W. Becher".
- O'Neill, Eliza, 1791-1872, Ballygiblin - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 28 November 1860; HWD 06.028; autograph letter signed
  signed, "E W Becher".
- Ormathwaite, John Benn Walsh, Baron, 1798-1881, Warfield Park, Bracknell - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 March 1873; HWD 09.055; autograph letter signed
- Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 07.114; autograph letter signed
  including a copy of a letter from Jérôme Bonaparte to his nephew.
- Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.001; autograph note signed
- Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852, Chambourcy - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 19 November 1849; HWD 07.117; autograph letter signed
- Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 10.070; autograph letter signed
- Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 7 July 1847; HWD 07.110; autograph letter signed
- Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852, 38 Rue de la Ville [d'Eugene?] - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 17 January 1850; HWD 07.113; autograph letter signed
- Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852, Waterloo Hotel - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.102; autograph letter signed
- Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 01.103; autograph letter signed
- Orsay, Alfred Guillaume Gabriel, comte d', 1801-1852 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 5 January 1852; HWD 05.005; autograph letter signed
  in French.
- Osborne, Ralph, 1808-1882, House of Commons - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 22 July 1861; HWD 01.100; autograph letter signed
- Osborne, Ralph, 1808-1882 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 4 December [no year]; HWD 10.036; autograph letter signed
- Osborne, Ralph, 1808-1882, Newtown Anner, Clonmel - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 May 1864; HWD 01.061; autograph letter signed
- Osborne, Ralph, 1808-1882, Newtown Annex Clonmel - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 15 February 1861; HWD 01.101; autograph letter signed
- Osborne, W. G. (William Godolphin), 1804-1899, Gogmagog Hills, Cambridge - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1 November 1869; HWD 06.081; autograph letter signed
- Osborne, W. G. (William Godolphin), 1804-1899, Brandon Suffolk - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, "Tuesday"; November 1868; HWD 06.084; autograph letter signed
- Paget, James, Sir, 1814-1899, 1 Harewood Place, Hanover Square, W - to [?], 3 April 1886; HWD 05.034; autograph note signed
- Paget, James, Sir, 1814-1899, 1 Harewood Place, Hanover Square, W - to Howard, Mr, 23 June 1886; HWD 05.036; autograph letter signed
  re: Lord Winchilsea.
- Palmerston, Emily Lamb, Viscountess, 1787-1869, Park Lane - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 June [no year]; MISC 3503; autograph letter signed
- Palmerston, Emily Lamb, Viscountess, 1787-1869, Broadlands - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 8 February 1869; HWD 09.002; autograph letter signed
- Palmerston, Emily Lamb, Viscountess, 1787-1869 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, HWD 04.011; autograph letter signed
- Palmerston, Emily Lamb, Viscountess, 1787-1869, Picadilly, HWD 06.101; autograph letter signed
- Palmerston, Emily Lamb, Viscountess, 1787-1869 - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 10 December 1866; HWD 04.100; autograph letter signed
- Peel, Adelaide Dugdale, d. 1890, 70, Eaton Place, S. W - to Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 27 February [no year]; HWD 05.080; autograph letter signed